fs.com 2019-08-08

# Privacy Policy | FS - Fiberstore

In order to provide FS services to you, we will ask you to provide personal data depending on how you interact with us (online, offline, over the phone, etc.). Personal data about our customers is an important part of our business. We will not sell, share or rent your information to third parties in any way other than what is disclosed in this statement.

## Personal Contact Information

This includes any information that would allow us to personally contact you, such as your name, delivery address, phone number, or email address. In some cases, this could include personal information that you give us about someone else (for example, if you provide a friend's name and email address for a share cart/product/saved items action).

We typically collect personal contact information in connection with a variety of activities, including website registration, email subscriptions, website community features, online purchases, customer service inquiries, and consumer feedback. If you create an account with us, your personal contact information may be stored under your account profile.

## Account Sign-in Information

This refers to any information that is required for you to establish a unique account with us or for us to give you access to your specific account profile. Examples may include your email address, user name and password.

We only collect unique sign-in information for those activities that require an account, such as general website registration, email subscriptions, and website community features. Your sign-in information, especially your password, should be kept confidential and never shared with anyone else. To change your login email address or password, sign in to the relevant account setting section of our website.

## Demographic Information

This includes any information that describes your demographic or psycho-graphic characteristics. Examples may include your geographic location (e.g., post code, country/region, mobile location), frequently viewed products, and preferred language.

We typically collect demographic information in connection with a variety of activities, including general website registration, customer service inquiries, and site browsing information. If you create an account with us, you may be allowed to modify certain demographic information stored under your account or in your browser. For demographic information stored under your profile on a third party social network (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin, Google+ etc.), see separate paragraph on “Social Network Information”.

## Technical Computer Information

This includes any information about the computer system or other technological device that you may be using to access one of our websites, applications or online services. We typically collect this information through automated technologies such as cookies and tags. Examples of technical computer information may include your computer’s IP address, operating system type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), and web browser type. View more in Cookies and Contents of Third Parties.

## Website Usage Information

This includes information about how you use and navigate our websites, applications and online services, including which links you click on, which pages or content you view and for how long, and other similar information and statistics about your interactions with our website or application (e.g., date and time of visit, which site you came from, frequently viewed products, and site activities, etc.).

This information is captured using automated tracking technologies such as cookies or Yandex Metrica, and may also be collected through the use of third party tracking services (such as Google Analytic) that collect data in aggregate (such as number of visits to a particular page, or the amount of time spent on a web site). We may also use these programs, such as Yandex Metrica, to capture information about how users respond to certain emails (e.g., time the email is opened, where user links to from the email, etc.). Please view more in Cookies and Contents of Third Parties.

## Consumer Feedback

This includes information that you voluntarily share with us about your experience in using our products and services, including our websites and applications. Examples may include unsolicited reviews and suggestions, or other questions and feedback related to our products. We typically collect this information in the form of product review, Q&A, requesting stock, getting a quote, creating a case, submitting technical solutions, Google customer review and customer service through email or hotline.

## Social Network Information

This refers to any information that is part of your profile on a third party social network (such as but not limited to Facebook/Twitter) and that you allow the third party social network to share with us. Examples include your basic account information (e.g., name, email address, gender, birthday, current city, profile picture, user ID, list of friends, etc.) and any other additional information or activities that you permit the third party social network to share with third party application developers. For example, we may receive your social network profile information (or parts of it) every time you download or interact with a FS application on a social network such as Facebook or Twitter or every time you use a social networking feature that is integrated within a FS (such as Post FS product to Facebook, share news from FS Blog to Facebook, etc.).

To learn more about how your information from a third party social network may be obtained by us (or other third party application developers), please visit the website of the relevant social network. You further acknowledge using your personal information to match information with a social network for advertising purposes.

## Payment Information

This includes any information that you use to make a purchase, such as your credit/debit card details (cardholder name, card number, expiration date, etc.), other payment information if you choose to pay by Credit/Debit Card/PayPal/Wire Transfer. This also includes the billing name and address associated with your form of payment.

## Personal Information from Children

Personal information will not be collected by any person who is known by FS to be under the age of eighteen (18) without the consent of a parent or legal guardian. Persons under age eighteen (18) may only provide personal information with the involvement and consent of a parent or legal guardian.

## Mobile Information

If you access our website or application via a mobile device such as a smart-phone, the collected information may also include your phone's unique device ID, brand, type, operator company and operating system.

We use personal information to better understand our customers’ interests and needs, to complete purchase transactions and fulfill orders and to consistently improve quality of products.

We may use your personal information in following ways:

## Account maintenance

We may use your personal information to maintain your accounts with us, including administering any consumer satisfaction or products optimization programs that are associated with your account. This typically involves the use of personal information that was originally collected to set up your account (e.g., personal contact information, payment information, delivery address, account login information, demographic information, etc.) or purchase history.

## Customer Service

We may collect and use your personal information to provide you customer service, including responses to your inquiries, stock request, quote sheet, technical solution request, etc. This typically requires the collection and use of certain personal contact information (such as your name, phone or email address) and information regarding the reason for your inquiry (e.g. order status, technical issue, product question/complaint, etc.). Customer service may be provided through various forms of communication, including email correspondence, call centre support, and live chat online.

## Product Improvement and Customization

We may collect and use your information so we can constantly improve our products, tailor them to your needs, and come up with new product ideas. This mostly involves the collection and use of demographic information and consumer feedback.

## Product and Service Improvement

We may collect and use your personal information to encourage you to be more actively engaged with our products and services (including our websites and applications), thereby increasing overall brand engagement and improving our products/services. This mostly involves the collection, use, and publication of consumer-generated content (such as product/order reviews).

And we will send an email to you and invite you to write a review about our products and services in this transaction. If you choose to join in the Google customer review program, you will also receive an email from Google about it.

## Third Party Social Networking

We may collect and use your personal information when you interact with third party social networking features such as “Post to Facebook” or “Tweet to Twitter”. These features may be integrated in our sites or applications for the purposes of allowing you to share FS product/news with your friends, or other stated purposes. If you use these features, we may have the ability to obtain certain information about you from your social networking profile (see “Social network information”). You can learn more about how these features work, and the profile data we may obtain about you, by visiting the website of the relevant third party social network. 

## Website Improvement and Personalization

We may collect and use your information to improve and personalize your experience on our websites and applications. This is typically done through automated tracking technologies that collect and remember certain account login information, technical information, previous website usage information, and/or IP address. For example, we might remember your sign-in email address and password so you can quickly sign in next time when you visit our website. Based on this type of information, we may also show you specific FS content matched your country/region.

## Website Sharing Features (e.g., share cart/product/saved items with a friend)

We may request and use your personal information so you can use website sharing features, such as our share-with-a-friend features. These features allow you to easily share certain product information, saved items/carts, or shopping cart with your colleagues or friends. These features may also require the collection and use of your friends’ personal information (such as names and email addresses) so that the selected one-time message or content can be delivered to the proper recipients. In most cases, we do not retain the information provided. In some cases (for example, as part of a refer to-share-data program), we may store the information so we can track and conclude the referrals data. For other sharing features administered by third party social networks (such as Facebook’s “Share” and Twitter's “Tweet” features), please refer to the website of the relevant social network for additional information.

## Order Fulfillment

We may collect and use your personal information to process and deliver your orders, and to inform you about the status of your orders. This could involve the collection and use of certain personal contact information, payment information, account login information, and/or other information related to your purchase (such as products ordered).

As payments, shipping and delivery are being fulfilled by a third party (bank, online payment company, or logistics company), we will share your personal information with them for the purposes of fulfillment of the order. You may, as a result, also receive communications from that third party (whether by email, SMS or other methods of communication) regarding the fulfillment of payment or delivery.

## Other General Purposes (e.g., website security, internal research)

We may collect and use your information for other general business purposes, such as to maintain the day-to-day operation and security of our websites and applications and to conduct internal records and demographic studies. These activities mostly require the collection and use of certain demographic information, technical computer information, website usage information, and consumer feedback.

We may use or disclose personal information in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorized to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to protect you, to comply with legal process or authorities, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of FS Wholesale, our Members, our employees or the public.

We may also share your personal information between:

* Our related companies (for example, our head office, UK branch office, etc.)

* Our service providers including IT service providers, delivery companies, live chat service providers, out-sourced call centres, and third party fulfillment contractors;

* Our professional advisers including our accountants, auditors and lawyers for particular purposes;

* Payment system operators and financial institutions;

* Government agencies if necessary or requested by law;

* Youtube Video Plugins;

* Those website analyse service providers and social media networking service plugins listed below: 

### Google Tag Manager 

On the basis of our legitimate interest (interest in the analysis, optimization and economic operation of our website), this website uses the Google Tag Manager provided by Google Inc. This service allows website tags to be managed through a single interface.

### Google (Universal) Analytics 

For the purpose of continuous optimization of our pages, we use Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. In this context, pseudonymised usage profiles are created and cookies are used. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website such as

Browser type / version,

Used operating system,

Referrer URL (the previously visited page),

Host name of the accessing computer (IP address),

Time of server request,

are transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there.

### Google AdWords 

Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on our website or applications. Through the targeting measures, we just want to display advertisement based on your actual interests or behavior-orientation.

### Yandex Metrica Web Analytics 

We use Yandex Metrica Web Analytics to get visual reports and video records of user activities on our websites or applications. It can help us track referer URL and evaluate the effectiveness of online advertisement.

### Google Customer Review 

Google Customer Reviews is a program that allows you to rate your purchase experience about our websites, products, or services. The rating that you give in your review can help other shoppers make an informed decision to purchase.

After you complete submitting an order, there will be a dialog box asking whether you are willing to share your opinion. If you have any concerns about safety of your personal information, just click "No". If you choose to opt-in the survey program from Google Customer Reviews, Google will send you one email a few days after your order has been delivered. As a result of your opting in, Google will collect your email address, order number, country and delivery information. But Google will never send any other emails or use your personal information for any other purposed (except from stated in this para).

### Social Networking Services (SNS) Plugins 

Concerning SNS providers in FS, it contains Facebook, Twitter, Google+, or Linkedin. When you visit a page of our website that contains such a plugin, your browser connects directly to the corresponding SNS servers. The content of the plugin is transmitted by the SNS company directly to your browser and integrated into the page. Through this integration, these SNS companies receive the information that your browser has accessed relevant pages, even if you do not have a SNS profile or are currently not signed in to SNS websites. This information (including your IP address) will be transmitted from your browser directly to a SNS server in the US and stored there.

If you are signed in to the SNS website, they can immediately assign your visit to our website with your SNS profile. If you interact with the plugins, for example, click the "Like/Tweet/+1/share" button or leave a comment, this information will be posted on your SNS profile, displayed to your friends and transmitted to the SNS server and stored there.

The purpose and scope of the information collection, the further processing and use of the personal information by SNS, your rights in this regard, and setting options for the protection of your privacy can be reset in the SNS websites.

* * *

We give you choices related to your personal information, and numerous methods to inform us of your decision. You can control your personal information that FS has obtained. You have the right to access, correct, or delete the personal data that we collect. You are also entitled to restrict or object, at any time, to the further processing of your personal information.

You have the right to receive your personal information in a structured and standard format and, where technically feasible, the right to have your personal data transmitted directly to a third party.

To protect the privacy and the security of your personal data, we may request data from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access such information, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal data we maintain.

You can always choose whether you wish to receive promotional emails, messages from FS. You can also access and clear your data through the FS privacy dashboard.

The acceptance of cookies is not necessary to access FS. However, we draw your attention that failure to accept cookies may limit some certain functions of our website. You can reset your browser to decline cookies at any time if you wish.

### What Are Cookies 

Cookies are small data files that are stored on your data carrier and record certain settings and data for exchange with our system via your browser.

In general, there are 2 different types of cookies:

* The so-called session cookies, that are deleted as soon as you close your browser;

* Temporary/permanent cookies, that are stored on your data carriers for a longer period or without limit.

### Which Cookies Are Used by FS 

Session cookies are used by us, which will be automatically deleted from your hard disk at the end of the browser session. Session cookies are needed, for example, to make the shopping-cart function available to you over several pages.

In addition to these we also make use of cookies that remain on your hard disk. On a subsequent visit it is then automatically recognized that you have previously visited FS, and let us know which input and settings you prefer. These temporary or even permanent cookies (lifespan of 1 day to 2 years) are stored on your hard disk and are automatically deleted after the pre-specified period.

### What Information Is Stored in The Cookies 

In the cookies used by FS, only anonymous data is stored. Your name, your IP address and other personal information that might be used to trace you directly are not placed in the cookie. On the basis of the cookie technology we receive only anonymous information, relating for example to which of our shop carts have been visited, which products were viewed, etc.

### Why Does FS Use Cookies 

This information will never be used to identify you personally but only help us to recognize and remember your interests so that we can customise content and enhance the personalization of your online shopping experience. For example, after the initial set-up and sign in, these cookies enable you to come back to our site again without having to sign in each time.

With this technology, we can recognize your interests, present specific products/services to make our website more user-friendly, more effective and more secure. The content will be based on information obtained from a connection to click-stream analysis (for example, it is based on the fact that during the past few days only Fibre Optic Cables has been viewed). Our aim is to make your shopping experience as comfortable as possible.

### How Can You Prevent The Storage of Cookies 

In your browser you can adjust the setting that storage of cookies is only permissible when you agree to it, and thereby prevent the further storage of cookies in the future.

FS shall regularly review the sufficiency of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify and change the Privacy Policy at any time.

Subject to your rights at law, you agree to be bound by the prevailing terms of the Policy as updated from time to time on our Website. Any changes to this policy will be published on the Platform. By continuing to use our Platforms and/or services after the Policy has been amended, you hereby agree to be bound by the terms of such amended Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement or would like to contact us for any reason, you can do the following:

Email to [legal@fs.com](mailto:legal@fs.com), Call us at +1 (888) 468 7419, or Write to us at the following address:

FS.COM INC, 380 Centerpoint Blvd, New Castle, DE 19720, United States  
FiberStore Co., Limited, A115 Jinhetian Business Centre, No.329, Longhuan Third Rd, Longhua District, Shenzhen, 518109, China

Emails and letters should clearly state that you are making a data protection query, request or complain in the subject line to ensure the matter is dealt with expediently. We will strive to deal with any query, request or complaint promptly and fairly.
